After all these years, all your questions will finally be answered.
Hey Arnold! The Jungle Movie is a family, comedy,
animation film directed by Raymie Muzquiz.
When their trip to San Lorenzo takes a turn for the worst, Arnold and his classmate’s only hope of
getting home is retracing the dangerous path that led to Arnold's parents' disappearance.
Arnold (voice), played by Mason Cotton.
Gerald (voice), played by Benjamin Flores Jr..
Helga (voice), played by Francesca Marie Smith.
Phoebe (voice), played by Anndi McAfee.
Eduardo (voice), played by Carlos Alazraqui.
La Sombra (voice), played by Alfred Molina.
Hey Arnold!: The Movie is a 2002 American animated adventure comedy film based
on the animated television series created by Craig Bartlett.
It was directed by Tuck Tucker and written by Bartlett and Steve
Viksten, with music by series composer Jim Lang.
The film stars Spencer Klein, Francesca Smith, Jamil Walker Smith, Dan
Castellaneta, Tress MacNeille, Paul Sorvino, and Jennifer Jason Leigh.
The film follows Arnold, Gerald, and Helga on a quest to save their neighborhood from a
greedy developer who plans on converting it into a huge shopping mall.
The events of the film take place during the series' fifth and final season.
The project was originally developed as a television film titled Arnold Saves the Neighborhood, but
following successful test screenings, Paramount Pictures decided on a theatrical release.
Hey Arnold!: The Movie was released in theaters on June 28, 2002,
and received unfavorable reviews from critics.
The film grossed $15 million against a production budget of $3–$4 million.
A made for television sequel, Hey Arnold!: The Jungle Movie, aired in 2017.
The film explores themes of sequel, based on cartoon,
series finale, based on tv series.
The tone is lighthearted.